best-amateur-videos.com 2019-12-08

# CCBill Consumer Privacy Policy

## Instructions

CCBill, LLC ("CCBill") needs to gather and use certain information about individuals. This information can include customers, suppliers, business contacts, employees and other people the organization has a relationship with or may need to contact. This policy describes how this personal data must be collected, handled and stored to meet the company’s data protection standards – and to comply with the law.

## Why this Policy Exists

This data protection policy ensures CCBill:

  * Complies with data protection law and follows good practice
  * Protects the rights of staff, customers and partners
  * Is transparent about how it stores and processes individuals personal data
  * Protects itself from the risk of a data breach

## The General Data Protection Regulation

The EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) replaces the Data Protection Directive 95/46/EC and was designed to harmonize data privacy laws across Europe, to protect EU citizens’ data privacy and to reshape the way organizations across the world approach data privacy. The GDPR aims primarily to give control back to citizens and residents over their personal data and to simplify the regulatory environment for international business by unifying the regulation within the EU.

## What is "Personal Data"?

"Personal data" is defined in both the Directive and the GDPR as any information relating to a person who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of that person. So in many cases online identifiers including IP address, cookies and so forth will now be regarded as personal data if they can be (or are capable of being) without undue effort linked back to the data subject.

1\. Information collection and tracking

1.1. When you visit our website.

You can visit our website (www.ccbill.com) without giving away your personal information. CCBill uses Google Analytics and Cookies in order to improve our service, user experience and analyze how our website is used. Aside from the approximate location (IP address), the information collected by Google Analytics is mostly anonymous traffic data including browser information, device information, language. We do not collect additional information, such as your age, gender, interests, bank details or clickstream.

The collected information is used to provide an overview of how people are accessing and using the CCBill website. It is not used for any additional purpose, such as to profile those who access our website.

2\. When you contact us

While you can use our website without giving out your personal information, once you contact us via the CCBill website, CCBill collects information about you.

The information you fill in (personal information such as your name, email address, organization) will be processed and stored so that it is possible for us to contact and respond to your request, and/or allow you access to our services.

2.1. Recruitment

If you apply for a job with CCBill, we will collect, process and store the information you have sent us for recruitment-related purposes, such as contacting you. Additionally, CCBill may keep your data for a period of time for the purpose of considering you for a different opportunity.

3\. Social media plug-ins

Our website features two plug-ins for easy sharing and following our social media pages: Facebook, operated by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA; and LinkedIn, operated by LinkedIn, 2029 Sterling Court Mountain View, CA 94043 United States.

Being on our website does not automatically result in sharing data on these social media networks. These plugins remain inactive (idle) until clicked upon. Once clicked upon, you will be taken to the said social media networks with their own specific privacy policies you are recommended to consult.

4\. Information Security

When CCBill collects information about you, we also make sure that your information is protected from unauthorized access, loss, manipulation, falsification, destruction or unauthorized disclosure. This is done through appropriate technical measures.

5\. Access to Information

You have the right to request access to the information we have on you. You can do this by contacting us at [dpo@ccbill.com](mailto:dpo@ccbill.com). We will make sure to provide you with a copy of the data we process about you. In order to comply with your request, we may ask you to verify your identity. We will fulfil your request by sending your copy electronically, unless the request expressly specifies a different method. For any subsequent access request, we may charge you with an administrative fee.

6\. Information Correction & Deletion

If you believe that the information we have about you is incorrect, you are welcome to contact us so we can update it and keep your data accurate. Any data that is no longer needed for the purposes specified in Information Collection and Use or for any Regulatory Reporting purposes will be deleted.

If you have any queries about the personal data that CCBill stores, you can simply contact us at [dpo@ccbill.com](mailto:dpo@ccbill.com).

7\. When this Privacy Policy applies

This Privacy Policy is applicable to the services offered by CCBill directly via our website. Our website may contain links to other websites. Once redirected to another website, this Policy is no longer applicable.

This version of the Privacy Policy is effective from January 2019.

8\. Do We Share Personal Data?

CCBill may share your Personal Data (name, address and email) with unaffiliated third parties as provided in this section of the Privacy Policy. The reason we share this information with your information varies based on the relationship CCBill maintains with the respective party, which include the following reasons:

**Financial Institutions** : CCBill may share Personal Data with Financial Institutions that we have partnered with to jointly create and offer a product or service. These financial institutions are not allowed to market and/or offer other products or services other than those offered by CCBill.

**Parties to Transactions** : CCBill may share information with parties to your transaction, including the operators of websites delivering your purchased product. This information includes:

  * Personal Data necessary to facilitate the transaction;
  * Information to help other participants resolve disputes and detect and prevent fraud;
  * Aggregated data and performance analytics to help merchants better understand Users and to help Merchants enhance Users’ experience.

**As Permitted or Required by Law** : CCBill may share information about you with third parties for CCBill’s business purpose or required by law, including:

  * Comply with the law, legal process or regulations; 
  * Law enforcement authorities or other government officials, or other third parties, subject to a subpoena, court order or other legal process or requirement applicable to CCBill.
  * Investigate violations of our Consumer Agreement or other legal terms applicable to any service;
  * To help assess and manage risk and prevent fraud against us, our Users and fraud involving our service provided, including fraud that occurs at or involves consumers and merchants. 
  * Protect our property, Services and legal rights; 
  * In connection with shipping and related services for purchases made using a service.
  * To support our audit, compliance and corporate governance functions.

9\. Changes

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy. We constantly review our Privacy Policy and strive towards making it better. CCBill will not reduce your rights stated in this Policy without asking for explicit prior consent to the changes. All changes to our Privacy Policy will be available on this website. You can access the previous versions of this Policy [here](https://ccbill.com/gdpr/gdpr_v1.html).

10\. To Sum Up

In accordance with applicable law, we only collect a limited amount of information about you that is necessary for improving our service. We do not use profiling, we do not sell or in any other way spread your data to third parties, and we do not use your data for purposes other than what we specified. We also make sure that your data is stored securely. We delete all information deemed no longer necessary. We constantly review our Privacy Policy in order to make it better and protect you more.

11\. You can contact us at any time to:

  * Request access to information that CCBill has about you
  * Correct any information that CCBill has about you
  * Delete information that CCBill has about you

If you have any additional questions about CCBill’s collection and storage of data, please contact us at:

CCBill  
2353 West University Drive  
Tempe, Arizona USA  
85281  

## Glossary of terms

Cookies

Cookies are small files or other pieces of data which are downloaded or stored on your computer or other device that can be tied to information about your use of our website (including certain third party services and features offered as part of our website).

Device

A device is what you use to reach our website, such as a smartphone, tablet or computer.

IP address

Internet Protocol (IP) address is a number that is connected to your device. An IP address can be used to determine the location of your device typically within a 40km radius, thus not being an exact determination of your location. IP addresses are basically how the Internet functions.

Personal information Personal information is information that can identify you. This can be your name, email, contact information or other type of information that can be traced back to you.
